

Andrea Ho

UX/UI DESIGNER

andrea.ks.ho@gmail.com 778.882.7372 andreaho.ca

SKILLS

User Experience Design

Market Research

Empathic Research

Competitor Analysis

Human-Centered Design

Interaction Design

Rapid Prototyping

Usability Testing

UI Design

Graphic Design

HTML5/CSS3

TOOLS

Sketch

Creative Cloud Suite

Invision

Persona

Empathy Map

Storyboarding

Feature Matrix

Customer Journey Map

How Might We

Card Sorting

Sitemap

Userflow

Wireframes

Hi-fidelity Mockups

INTERESTS

Acrylic Painting

Photography

Playing Badminton

Dragon Boating

SUMMARY

My mission is to create a happier, stress-free, educational environment for everyone through user experience. With my background in marketing, I place heavy emphasis on understanding how people behave in all of my design projects. It is only through heavy knowledge of humans when we start to solve the world's problems.

PROJECTS

Trekit

Jun 2017 - July 2017

- Designed a social mobile app that allows for quick and easy sharing of memories created from travellers' trips
- Tackled an Information Architecture taxonomy issue, discovered after multiple rounds of usability testing, which was solved by creating a visual representation and a sitemap
- Iterated multiple versions of wireframes adjusted from user testing
- Created a brand that aligned with Trekit's personality of excitement, curiosity, individuality and adventure

NASA Vacations

May 2017 - Jun 2017

- Implemented a personalized screen for every passenger on the NASA aircraft for space tourism
- Focused heavily on understanding the users through user interviews, personas, empathy maps, and customer journey maps, which enhanced functionality and usability for key audiences
- Conducted user experience research through interviews and usability testing using low and high fidelity prototypes

ShopFresh

Feb 2017 - May 2017

- Designed a responsive website for an online grocery store catered to busy university students using Sketch
- Utilized the user data gathered through methods such as user interviews, market research and secondary research to make informed design decisions
- Tested interactive prototypes to iterate and improve design wireframes
- Created a brand that best represents Shopfresh's three main elements: freshness, quality and cleaniness

A Design A Day for 100 Days

Feb 2017 - Jun 2017

- Created a graphic, 3D and user interface design everyday for 100 days
- Recorded my design process through a diary coded on my personal website

EXPERIENCE

Marketing Intern, Boucher Institute of Naturopathic Medicine

Vancouver, BC

Jun 2016 - Aug 2016

- Created a tactical brief for the Professional Development Project and 7 copy decks for the redesign of poster advertisements
- Identified ways to gather popularity on social media for the naturopathic medical school by accumulating other university
- Designed 4 different catalogue covers for the clinic and faculty institute using Adobe Illustrator
- Worked closely with the graphic designer to create a cohesive program for the incoming medical students, including logo design and branding

Marketing Associate, Miss World Canada

Vancouver, BC

Jan 2015 - May 2015

- Responsible for collecting sponsors and potential candidates across Canada
- Continuously reviewing and promoting ticket sales before the actual event, as well as contacting the marketing manager and the CEO for constructive feedback

EDUCATION

User Experience Design, Designlab UX Academy

San Francisco, CA

2017

 ${\it Bachelor\ of\ Commerce\ -\ Marketing,\ University\ of\ British\ Columbia}$

Vancouver, BC

2013 - 2017